{
    "id": "d73c2dcd85004f80811d9e76d6a3aca7",
    "title": "Sequence of Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Suddenly she gave a loud scream and ……………………… to the ground.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fell",
                "has fallen",
                "had fallen"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7bec1696a899490b8a8b8f056aec9f3d"
        },
        {
            "question": "After questioning he ………………… to go home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "allowed",
                "had allowed",
                "was allowed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d5107eaeb9e342caa10b841705971aad"
        },
        {
            "question": "They would have won if they …………………. a bit harder.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "played",
                "have played",
                "had played"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "896a789a14aa4872b58b30b1fb0493d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. to say that she disagreed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "heard",
                "was heard",
                "had heard"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b43168fd16aa475d9ac60f47bc70e65c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although they …………………… defeated, they did not lose heart.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "were",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6f534eac77f440768c9a2144deef7927"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our teacher taught us that virtue …………………… . its own reward.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f873f59f8400433485b8a8eb6dd85776"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher asked the boys whether they …………………… . the problems.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "solved",
                "have solved",
                "had solved"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9a69520d82954a4f84543f9e5c1180dd"
        },
        {
            "question": "He declared that he would not believe it even if he ……………………… it with his own eyes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "have seen",
                "had seen"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ef053a90cd6c48cc883dd47722f0cbc6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The room ……………………… but the police failed to find anything suspicious.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "searched",
                "was searched",
                "had searched"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "221f487e103a4e688e37ece2b4c0cb6c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The government has announced that taxes …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will raise",
                "will be raised",
                "would be raised"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "90a506fef368475ab57a435b826a3fef"
        }
    ]
}